Sorry.
不好意思
This is the staff restroom.
這裡是員工專用洗手間
Well…
那個…
I didn't expect my wish to come true soon.
居然 願望能夠實現呢
Excuse me, can you lend me a hand?
不好意思 能助我一臂之力嗎
(Metallic Rouge)
《金屬口紅》
Verde's id has been retrieved.
維杜的伊德已回收
Naomi Orthmann and Rouge Redstar have completed their mission on Mars,
直美・奧德曼與露瓊・雷德斯塔 結束了火星任務
and will return to Earth in about two days.
約在兩天後回到地球
Thank you.
謝謝
Deputy Director Junghardt.
容格哈特次長
Can I have a moment with you?
能打擾一下嗎
Don't you think people can see you through from the sky?
不覺得會被人從天空看穿嗎
Are you talking about the Visitor, X Noah?
來訪者 傑・諾亞嗎
They are no gods, after all.
他們又不是什麼神明
This is really good.
哎呀 這個真好喝
I think you are the one who sees me through.
我倒是覺得被妳看穿了
Minister Zhao.
趙部長
I got to this position because I trust my men.
我之所以能爬到這裡 是因為相信部下
I trust you no matter what you hide from me.
不管你瞞著我什麼 我都相信你
The real problem
真正麻煩的
is the external interference to the Aletheia.
是外部對真理部的干涉
I've received a report that they seem to have someone inside the Aletheia.
我有收到報告 部裡似乎有他們的內應
Is it an agent of the Ochrona?
是守護局的特務嗎
This matter must not be biased,
不能徇私
and do not hide anything from me.
也別對我有所隱瞞
Master.
老爺
Is your leg all right now?
您的腿傷已經不要緊了嗎
I'm fine, as you can see.
如你所見 好得很呢
Let's get wild in the dance hall tonight.
今晚就去舞廳瘋一下吧
Hi, the boy next room.
喔 住在隔壁的少年
Hi, sisters next room.
喔 是住隔壁的姐姐
Where are you going?
妳們要去哪裡
Swimming pool.
去游泳池
Staying on the ship for nearly two weeks makes us sluggish.
在船上待將近兩星期的話 身體會變遲鈍的
Aes, are you going with us?
艾斯要不要一起去
I can't swim.
我不會游泳
And I'm going to the library to return the books.
而且我要去圖書室還書
So this is the paper book.
咦 這就是傳聞中的紙本書啊
We can enjoy Earth's traditional culture on this ship.
聽說這艘船上 能享受到地球傳統文化的樣子
I love the smell of paper books.
我很喜歡書本紙張的味道
It stinks.
好臭
But I don't hate the smell.
但這味道並不討厭
Right?
對吧
We'll be on Earth in two more days.
再過兩天就到地球了啊
Your wife's waiting for you, right?
你太太在等你回家吧
Yes.
是啊
Are you yourself?
妳是自己嗎
Rouge Redstar.
露瓊・雷德斯塔
Are you free?
妳是自由的嗎
Rouge.
露瓊
The masked man named Puppetmaster
那個名叫操偶師的面具男
broke into my dream.
他闖進了我的夢裡
Dream?
夢裡…
What is it?
什麼樣的夢
In a place that feels nostalgic,
在個有種懷念感覺的地方…
there's someone in front of me who seemed familiar and strange.
身前有個好像熟識… 又好像不認識的人…
I don't remember it exactly.
我也不是記得很清楚…
Who is that person?
那個人到底是誰啊…
What?
咦
Aes.
艾斯
Aes, you're amazing.
艾斯 不錯嘛
Didn't you say you can't swim?
你不是說你不會游泳嗎
If you mistake me for Aes, it would make me want to kill you.
把我錯當成艾斯會讓我想殺人的
What?
啊
Are you Aes's twin sister?
難不成妳是艾斯的雙胞胎姊姊…
I am Alice.
艾莉斯
You are Rouge and Naomi, right?
妳們是露瓊跟直美對吧
Aes told me that there are two really beautiful girls living next room.
艾斯有跟我說 隔壁住了兩位超漂亮大姐姐
That Aes is quite nice.
那個艾斯人不錯嘛
But saying you are really beautiful is quite overexaggerated.
說超漂亮有點言過其實
At best, you two are a not-ugly-looking duo.
頂多就是長得不醜的二人組吧
Has he lost his mind?
艾斯的眼睛是被土蝨塞住了嗎
He has a problem with aesthetics.
審美觀整個崩壞了
Not-ugly-looking…
長得不醜…
Duo…
二人組…
I went to Mars specifically,
都難得去到火星了
and now I'm asked to fly back to Earth.
居然又要我飛回地球
We had to do so.
這也沒辦法
We have to obey the order to return.
得服從歸隊命令才行
That red guy is on Mars.
那個紅色傢伙就在火星
And,
而且
there's a black guy who's not on the record.
還出現了不在記錄上的黑色傢伙
What are those Aletheia guys
那些真理部的傢伙
hiding?
到底在隱瞞著什麼
Hi.
嗨
Noid.
諾伊德
-What? -No way.
-咦 -不會吧
Hmm?
嗯?
I heard there was a murder.
聽說發生殺人案件了
Murder?
殺人案件
Someone got killed?
有人被殺了嗎
The murderer is Reggie Avan, 38 years old,
凶手是雷吉・亞本 38歲
179 cm, 68 kg,
179公分 68公斤
a blond white male, currently on the run.
是個金髮白人男性 現在逃走中
For your safety, please stay in your rooms.
為確保乘客安全 請乘客待在房內 不要外出
What should we do?
咦 那怎麼辦
We had no choice.
沒辦法
REGGIE AVAN
(雷吉・亞本)
Let go of me.
放開我
What did I do?
我到底做了什麼
Reggie Avan.
雷吉・亞本
I'm arresting you for the murder of Mark Johnson.
我要以殺害馬克・強生 的嫌犯身分逮捕你
What?
咦
Mark is dead?
你說馬克死了
No way.
不會的…
Aren't you the one who killed him?
人不就是你殺的嗎
Why do I have to kill him?
我為什麼非殺他不可
I've been in the casino up until now.
我到剛剛為止 人都在賭場裡啊
I am not lying.
我沒有騙你
I've lost almost 2 000 credits since this morning.
我從早上開始 就輸掉近2000信用點數了
This is a footage of the casino at the time of the murder.
這是案發當時的賭場畫面
What exactly is going on?
到底是怎麼回事
We can only assume one person appeared in different places at the same time.
只能判斷在同一時間裡 同一個人物出現在兩個地點
MOVIE I heard there was a murder.
(影城) 聽說發生殺人案件
That's horrible.
真是可怕
I heard we reception staff have to go back to our rooms when we are done here.
聽說這裡收拾好後 接待人員也要先回房待命
It's really horrible.
真的是…很可怕呢
What?
咦
That woman is the witness.
那名女性就是目擊者
You are now a witness,
您現在是案件目擊者
obliged to cooperate with our…
有義務配合我們的調…
Can you talk?
能夠說話嗎
You saw the murderer, right?
妳看到凶手了對吧
She looked exactly like Miss Cecil, right?
她長得跟塞希爾小姐一模一樣是嗎
Yes,
嗯
but it's not right.
但是不對
Although they looked exactly the same,
雖然臉長得一模一樣
that person is not Cecil.
但那個人不是塞希爾
Why do you think so?
為什麼這麼認為
Because she smiled.
因為她笑了…
Smiled?
笑了?
She had a really nasty smile.
她露出了非常噁心的笑容
Cecil would never smile like that.
那個人才不是塞希爾
So tasty!
好好吃喔
Is it okay we don't stay in the room?
不待在房裡沒關係嗎
When we return to Earth, we have to begin our daily work.
回到地球後就要開始勞動的每一天
I can't stay in my room right now.
我怎麼能在這種時候待在房裡啦
Is it okay that you're here?
妳們在這裡沒有關係嗎
What?
咦
A…
艾…
Aes
艾斯
or Alice?
還是艾莉斯
You have seen Alice, right?
妳們見到艾莉斯啦
You are Aes.
是艾斯啊
You two are really alike.
你們真的很像呢
What? We're not alike at all, okay?
哪裡像 根本就沒有好嗎
Then why are you here?
那艾斯又為什麼在這裡
We can't leave the room for now because of the murder,
因為可能會因殺人案 不能走出房間
so Alice asked me to get some food.
艾莉斯要我去拿些食物
She's excellent at bossing me around.
真的是很會使喚人
Why do the movies stop playing?
電影中止放映是什麼意思
Because there was a murder.
就說是因為發生了案件…
Didn't you see this strong Nean?
你是沒看到這強壯的涅安嗎
I have a bodyguard with me, and whatever the murder is,
我有保鑣跟著 管你是發生了什麼案件
I'm the one who spent a large amount of money.
我可是花了大錢的客人啊
-Let's go, Huey. -Is that difficult guest
-我們走 休伊 -那個奧客不是火星巴士上的大叔嗎
-Yes. -the man from the Mars bus?
-是
So he's also boarded the ship.
原來他也上了船啊
I'd rather meet a murderer than him.
比起殺人犯 我更不想遇上他啊
Aes, it's not safe to let you go back to your room alone.
艾斯 讓你一個人回房也不太好
Let's head back together.
我們一起回房去吧
Say hello to Alice.
好好照顧艾莉斯吧
You can't leave the room.
不可以離開房間喔
Goodbye.
嗯 再見
I didn't expect to see you again in a place like this.
想不到會在這種地方再見到妳啊
Well.
呃
Are you also from Aletheia?
妳也是真理部的人嗎
Well…
啊 那個…
Yes.
對啊
We've done our job, and now we're on a nice vacation.
我們完成了任務 現在正在爽休中
Is there a problem?
怎麼了嗎
Perfect.
正好
Naomi Orthmann.
直美・奧德曼
I'm arresting you on suspicion of murder.
我要以殺人嫌犯的身分逮捕妳
(Episode 6: Nameless Guest)
(6 無名之客)
Well…
這…
What the hell?
這什麼鬼啊
Every crime scene is more or less like this.
每個案發現場都差不多是這樣
After that, the footage cuts out, and we lose track of the murderer.
之後影像都會中斷 無法追蹤凶手的去向
Two identical people appeared in different locations.
兩個一模一樣的人出現在不同地點
Is it the so-called doppelganger?
會是所謂的二重身嗎
What is it?
那是什麼東西
Just don't ask.
你別問
Anyway, arresting you is just a precaution.
總之這算是以防萬一
Sorry.
不好意思啊
There are two Naomi.
有兩個直美…
Which one is the real one?
哪個才是真的啊
The one with you, of course.
當然是跟妳在一起的這一個啊
And, are you kidding me?
還有 這是在開什麼玩笑
Honestly, I don't understand it at all.
老實說我也完全搞不懂
Then unlock these handcuffs.
那就快把這副手銬解開啊
I don't trust people from the Aletheia.
我信不過真理部的人
After all, someone said to tell me who the red guy really is,
畢竟不知道是誰說 會告訴我紅色傢伙的真實身分
and then she just ran off.
結果竟然跑得不見人影
When this case is resolved, I have a bunch of questions for you.
等這個案子解決了以後 我有一堆問題要問妳
Hmm?
嗯?
Come…
來 把 我…
find me.
找出來吧
Wow.
哇
Hell Giallon is on this ship.
黃泉的迦隆就在這艘船上
I think so.
我想也是
It can't be wrong.
不會錯的
This series of crimes is a murder game he set up.
這一連串的犯行 是迦隆設下的殺人遊戲
If we play the game, we'll play right into his hands.
要是蹚這趟渾水 就會正中他的下懷
Our job is a secret that no one knows,
我們的工作是無人能知的秘密
even Minister Zhao.
是連趙部長都不知道的機密任務
But…
可是…
We are about to arrive on Earth.
馬上就要抵達地球了
Stay out of anything and don't make a fuss.
別去管任何事 不要引起騷動
It's part of our mission to get back to Gene quietly.
低調地回到吉恩身邊 也是我們的任務之一
The distinguished Ochrona detective will handle this matter.
優秀的守護局探員大人 會處理這件事
Just stay in your room.
妳就在房裡乖乖待著…
No way.
我不要這樣
What?
什…
I don't want to see you being suspected as a murderer.
我不想看到直美被人懷疑是殺人犯
Knowing that he's going to kill someone, yet I just stay in my room and do nothing.
明知道他會去殺害別人 卻還要待在房裡袖手旁觀
I hate it.
我討厭這樣的自己
A body of the ship's crew member was found in an airport restroom.
在機場的洗手間裡 發現了這艘船的船員屍體
Who is he?
他的身分呢
Well…
那個…
The deceased crew member is named Rob Ekatz.
遇害船員名叫羅布・艾卡茲
This is a search request from the Mars Terminal police.
這是火星航站警方發來的搜查通知
Maybe they have made a mistake.
他們是不是搞錯了啊
He's been working room service since we set off.
啟程之後 他就一直在執行客房服務工作
He's not a ghost.
總不可能是鬧鬼吧
That's true.
說得也是
I've seen him too.
我也有見到他
He's the one who appeared near the first crime scene.
是出現在第一起案發現場附近的人
Where is Ekatz now?
艾卡茲現在人在哪裡
2 minutes and 32 seconds ago,
在2分32秒前
we lost sign of Rob Ekatz in the ship.
就無法在船內確認到 羅布・艾卡茲這名男子的身影
Is he really a ghost?
難道真的鬧鬼了嗎
Impossible.
怎麼可能
No way.
不會的…
But apart from this…
但除了這種可能…
Ash, take a look at this.
亞許 請看這個
This is a live footage.
這是即時影象
Is this the footage from before the murder?
這次是動手前的畫面嗎
Wait.
妳等一下
Noid.
諾伊德
Find out what Ekatz weighed when he boarded the ship.
去查一下艾卡茲上船時的體重
He went to the library disguised as me.
他變成我的樣子去到了圖書室
Wait, it's the real me, I am the real one.
等一下 是本尊 我是本尊啦
Look.
妳看
Well…
那個…
Excuse me.
不好意思
I wonder if it's too late. What if she's Giallon?
有沒有可能已經那個了 眼前的那個其實是迦隆呢
Probably.
並非不可能
Are we going to do it?
要動手嗎
Oh, it's you.
哎呀 是妳們啊
Sorry.
不好意思
I turn off my hearing aid when I want some quiet time.
我想一個人靜一靜時 就會關掉助聽器
It's my secret to avoid my noisy husband.
這是我逃避聒噪先生的秘訣
Don't tell anyone.
別說出去喔
It's the real one.
是本尊耶…
I definitely won't quit smoking.
我絕對…不會戒菸的
Detective Ash.
亞許探員
There's been another murder.
又發生一起殺人案了
That's right.
這樣才對嘛
I'm Rouge, in the prime of my youth.
我是正值春青年華的露瓊
Ash, what's wrong?
亞許 你怎麼了
Press here.
壓住這裡
This is in front of the library. Get the doctor here now.
這裡是圖書室前 馬上派急救小組過來
Alright, go chase…
好了 妳快去追…
You…
啊 妳…
Thank you.
謝啦
Wait, you…
等一下 妳那個…
Darn it.
可惡…
That's why I hate the Aletheia.
就是這樣我才討厭真理部…
Naomi.
直美
Shoot now!
快開槍
Well, but which one is the real one?
講是這樣講 哪個才是本尊啊
Can't you tell?
妳看不出來嗎
Now let's get started on the Rouge quiz.
那麼 露瓊大問答 搶答題
Question.
提問
What's 7+7/7+7*7-7?
7加7除以7加7乘以7減7 等於多少
50.
等於50
Why?
為什麼
How did you tell?
妳怎麼知道是我
Rouge isn't that smart.
露瓊沒哪麼聰明
What's 7+7/7+7*7-7?
7加7除以7加7乘以7減7 等於多少
It doesn't matter.
那不重要啦
Got you!
有機可乘
We are from the Aletheia.
我們是真理部
ALETHEIA We will fully assist in this investigation.
(真理部) 現在要求你們全面配合
Nice to meet you.
謝謝各位
Did you find out how much the murderer weighed?
查出凶手的體重了嗎
It's under investigation as the detective requested.
現在正依探員的命令調查中
That old man is really good at it.
那個大叔挺有一套的嘛
Rob Ekatz, 26 years old, 182 cm tall.
羅布・艾卡茲 26歲 182公分
He weighed 82.2 kg at the time of boarding.
登船時的體重為82.2公斤
Gather and isolate those who weigh 82.2 kg on board.
將船上所有82.2公斤的人 集合隔離起來
It's you two again.
又是妳們兩個
The murderer of the serial killings is among you.
連續殺人事件的真凶就在你們之中
We're going to interrogate you…
現在開始要來審問你們…
I'm going to beat you now.
現在開始我要一個一個來揍你們
What?
咦…
Why?
為什麼
The one who can withstand my punch is Hell Giallon.
挨得了我的拳頭的人 就是黃泉的迦隆
They'd die if they are not the one.
挨不住的話會死人的吧
I can still control power of the punch.
這種力道我還是能控制的
And it's the fastest way, right?
而且這是最快的方法吧
Why do I have to take your punch?
為什麼非得挨妳的拳頭不可
My apologies.
得罪了
E-Enough. You are a girl.
妳…妳鬧夠了沒有 妳一個女孩子家…
You'll never get married this way.
這樣會嫁不出去的…
Does he weigh 82.2 kg?
他有82.2公斤嗎
He's the owner. The one weighing 82.2 kg is…
他是飼主 82.2公斤的是…
Are you going to beat Rubens too?
妳連魯本斯都要揍嗎
Rubens.
魯本斯
That's too much.
太過分了
You're the murderer.
妳才是殺人魔吧
How dare you'd kick such a cute dog!
居然用腳踹這麼可愛的狗…
R-Rubens?
魯…魯本斯
Stop pretending to be a pathetic dog.
別再裝可憐的狗狗了
Giallon.
迦隆
You're indeed funny.
妳果然很有意思
You're the funny one.
你才好笑吧
Alright.
好了
Please follow me.
請跟我來吧
Ash, you can't get up.
不能起來 亞許
I've always wanted to kill you myself.
我一直都很想親手殺了妳啊
The opponent who is a match for me,
好好地來體會一下
let me feel the thrill of potentially being killed by you, and I will…
這種與和自己不相上下的對手過招 隨時可能會死在對方手上的感覺
So wishes do come true.
原來願望真的會實現啊
Whatever.
愛怎麼說隨便你
Your method of attack is too simple.
妳的攻擊方式太單純了
I've seen right through it from the start.
從剛剛開始就都被我看穿了
I'm not listening to a murderer.
我才不會聽殺人魔說話
Is it really okay for you to say such pretentious words?
妳說這種逞強的話真的好嗎
You can't avenge your loved ones like this.
妳這樣是無法為親人報仇的喔
What are you talking about?
你在說什麼
Literally.
就是字面上的意思
Is it really you?
果然就是你嗎
Did you do it?
就是你做的嗎
Correct.
答對了
Your father, Mr. Roy Junghardt,
妳的父親 羅伊・容格哈特老師
was killed by me, who was disguised as you.
就是我化成妳的樣子 動手殺掉的
Then take what you deserve.
那你就接受報應吧
Acting impulsively at the slightest provocation
一下子就變得這麼衝動
is your bad habit.
那就是妳的壞習慣
Goodbye, Rouge.
再見了 露瓊
The filthy meteor falls into hell.
骯髒的流星墜入地獄
Fantastic!
太棒了
Captain.
船長
The patrol boat has issued a command to stop.
巡視艇發來停船命令
Oh my, I've been looking for you.
真是的 找妳好久了
Thank you for your work.
辛苦了
Who are they?
他們是誰
Artificial Species Audit Department of the Ochrona.
守護局人造種監查部
Naomi?
直美?
Rouge Redstar.
露瓊・雷德斯塔
You have violated the artificial species utilization regulations, Article 5, Item 9.
妳違反了 人造種運用規定第5條9項條例
I'm taking you into custody now.
現在要將妳拘禁